# IEVA BROBERG

Junior Web Developer



www.github.com/EvaBroberg



www.linkedin.com/in/ieva-broberg

## **EXPERIENCE**

2019

#### IUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

IGNIS LTD

Working closely with Lead developer on different digital projects such as quizzes, games, web-apps and websites. Using HTML, CSS, JS, Wordpress. Being trained in PHP and NodeJS.

2017 - 2019

# CREATIVE ARTWORKER - RETOUCHER

SWOON EDITIONS

Worked with product designers and photographers, retouching product and lifestyle imagery, creating web assets and content for web and press. Used Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign.

2015 - 2017

#### TEXTILE DESIGNER- FOUNDER

BRUBERI TEXTILE STUDIO

Founded a textile design studio while living in Finland for a couple of years, Created, printed and sold the textile design for independent designers and fashion houses in trade shows across Europe.

## **EDUCATION**

2019

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT COURSE

**CODE INSTITUTE** 

Learning HTML, CSS, JS, Python, user-centric, interactive frontend development using bootstrap, Data-centric full-stack development using Flask and Django. The course will result in a globally recognized diploma in software development.

2010 - 2013

#### **BA ILLUSTRATION**

#### MIDDLESEX UNIVERSITY

Graduated with a bachelor degree, grade 2.1 in illustration. The course included modules of illustration, life drawing, animation, printmaking, bookbinding, history of art and more. During this course,

#### REFERENCE

#### DANIEL PAKOS

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER, IGNIS LTD

Please ask for contact details on consideration.

## ABOUT ME

I am a junior web developer who has found her passion for technology and coding after a seven year career within creative industry. I started my journey to tech by commiting to the extensive full stack development training with 'Code Institute' and progressed by working on personal projects, getting involved in coding communities/workshops and dedicating all of my time to learning and self-development. Driven by passion and interest in the field I have landed my first dev job within less than a year and I am excited about new opportunities and further progression on this newly found career path.

#### CONTACT

**22A** Hartfield Crescent SW19 3SD

**\** 07455079898

ievabroberg@gmail.com

#### SKILLS

••••• HTML

••••• CSS, SAAS

•••••• JS, jQuery

•••••• PYTHON, FLASK

•••••• REACT |S

•••••• PHOTOSHOP